Contact

courtneyeggers@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/courtney-eggers-06485189 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Neonatal Nursing
Nursing Education
Nursing Management

Languages English

Certifications
RNC-NIC

Courtney Eggers

Alternate Care Site CNO in Denver CO
Denver

Summary

Experienced Nursing Leader exploring project management positions in the Denver, CO region.

I am proud to say I am a leader in Neonatal Nursing. From providing all aspects of care to sick and premature babies, to developing future nurses through management and education, I am truly reminded how amazing my field is. I have also taken my desire to care for all individuals to Haiti, where I have completed medical relief trips.

My NICU Leadership skills include Professional RN Development, EMR Implementation and Evidence Based Practice Implementation.

Experience

Denver Health 4 years 5 months

Alternate Care Site Health Care Partner. CNO April 2020 - Present (5 months)

NICU Manager

April 2016 - Present (4 years 5 months)

Daily oversight of 26 Bed Level III NICU in Safety Net Hospital located in Denver CO.

Interim Pediatrics and Pediatric Intensive Care Unit Nursing Manager May 2018 - October 2018 (6 months)

Denver, CO

NICU RN Manager

In addition to permanent NICU Nursing Management responsibilites, provided interim leadership to 20 bed Pediatric floor and 8 bed Pediatric Intensive Care Unit with Trauma Designation

Overland Park Regional Medical Center 1 year 10 months

Page 1 of 3

June 2014 - March 2016 (1 year 10 months)

Overland Park, KS

Manage daily operations of 71 Bed Level III NICU in the Kansas City Metro Area, providing care to infants from 23 weeks gestation, ill term infants, and surgical patients.

Interim NICU Director March 2015 - July 2015 (5 months)

Oversee all operations of 71 bed Level III NICU, including Midwest Neonatal Transport Team and NICU Follow Up Clinic.

Research Medical Center
NICU RN Manager
February 2013 - June 2014 (1 year 5 months)
Kansas City MO

Provided nursing leadership for assessing, planning, implementing and evaluating patient care and safety in 20 bed Level III NICU located in inner city Kansas City, MO. Supervised over 20 direct reports while adhering to collective bargaining agreement.

Denver Health

8 months

NICU Clinical Nurse Educator July 2012 - February 2013 (8 months)

Ensured staff remained competent in all skills needed to administer care to critically sick infants. Responsibilities included orientation, new initiative roll outs, and maintaining staff competency.

NICU Interim Manager July 2012 - February 2013 (8 months)

Oversaw financial and day to day operations of 23 bed Level III NICU located in Denver during Manager Vacancy.

Education

Western Governors University

Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.), Health/Health Care

Administration/Management · (2015 - 2016)

Denver School of Nursing